And what could I use as an example for our love?
There's nothing that can compare even from so high above
Looking down upon this endless ocean
Can you see the horizon?
Another end to a day we can't really call perfect
But that's okay even if we don't quite fit
Because love comes in all different flavors
And this is how we taste together
A little sweetness from you, baby three words will do
And every now and then some salt from the tears we shed
Don't you know that bitterness can disappear with one little kiss
From me to you and you to me
僕らの味といえばなんだろう？
やっぱり甘酸っぱいんだろう
絶妙の組み合わせじゃなくたって
十分美味しいんだね
飲み込んだらそんな顔しないで
みんな見てるから「美味しい！」と言って
誰だって舌バカになるさ
とりあえず味見はやめた
君に覚えてただきたい
このレシピは永遠の愛
A little sweetness from you, baby three words will do
And every now and then some salt from the tears we shed
Don't you know that bitterness can disappear with one little kiss
From me to you and you to me
知ってた？　僕はこの味をずっと探してたんだ
Of you
And me with you